There's a number of reasons you'd be potentially better
off breaking your app into different activities. Having a
single monolithic activity increases the complexity of your code,
making the creation and management of intent filters much
harder and making it more difficult to maintain, test,
and read your activity code. It also increases the
risk of tightly coupling independent components and makes it
much more likely to introduce security risks if the
single activity includes both sensitive information and information that's safe
to share. A good rule of thumb is to create a
new activity whenever the context changes. For example, displaying a
different kind of data, while switching from viewing to entering data.